The sun never sets on vengeance.
Catch the Bullet is a western, action film directed by Michael Feifer.
marshal Britt MacMasters returns from a mission to find his father
wounded and his son kidnapped by the outlaw Jed Blake.
Hot on their trail, Britt forms a posse with a
gunslinging deputy and a stoic Pawnee tracker.
But Jed and Britt tread dangerously close to the Red Desert’s Sioux territory.
Britt MacMasters, played by Jay Pickett.
Sheriff Wilkins, played by Peter Facinelli.
Dex, played by Tom Skerritt.
Chad, played by Mason McNulty.
Jed Blake, played by Gattlin Griffith.
Chaska, played by Cody Jones.
Lost Bullet (French: Balle perdue) is a 2020 French action thriller film directed by Guillaume Pierret, written by
Guillaume Pierret, Alban Lenoir and Kamel Guemra and starring Alban Lenoir, Nicolas Duvauchelle and Ramzy Bedia.
It was Pierret's first feature film.
Lost Bullet tells the story of an auto mechanic forced to go on the run
and battle corrupt police officers when framed for murder.
The action relies heavily on practical stuntwork and effects.
A Netflix production, the film was released globally on June 19, 2020.
It became a streaming hit and received generally
favorable reviews, launching a franchise.
A sequel, Lost Bullet 2, was released in 2022, and a third
film, Last Bullet, was released in 2025.